exploring? Oh, really?
Drawing is is a way for you to take in
the space?
Yes.
And do you think it helps you process it
and it Does it slow you down?
Cuz you have to take time to do a
drawing.
Yes. How
for, by the way?
This is a This is a 30-person YouTube
channel or 30-subscriber YouTube
channel. It's a It's a project that I
did after I graduated that's trying to
basically both
take conversations and treat them like
the museum  like experiences that
they are, that every conversation, every
idea is a portrait, and that in the same
way, sometimes you're too rushed for the
other person, sometimes you're too
distracted, you're not in the right
space. How is it that we treat with
museums or certain spaces with such
sacredness and that we slow down, that
we take the effort? Like imagine if I
could sit down with my friend and draw
them instead of say, "Oh, I don't have
time for you." Or You know what I mean?
Like that's a fantastic answer.
It also
I think that it also inspires our
conversations.
Yes.
Cuz I find that
it especially when I'm like traveling
it breaks down the conversation barriers
between strangers.
Yes.
Because people want to ask you what
you're drawing.
It's a secondary medium to motivate that
curiosity. Yes.